mysiteauditor.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy | MySiteAuditor.com

##  Information about our Organization and Website

This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from our community members and how that information may be used. Your privacy is important to us so please make sure you read this Privacy Policy carefully when using the website, tools, community, and any of our other services. By using our website you are accepting our policy described as the following:

Our privacy policy covers SEO Group, the tools, links, downloads, and all other services.

##  Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access 

You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.

##  Automatic Collection of Information

SEO Group does not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.

##  Data Collection and Purpose Specification

SEO Group does not share your email address or other personally identifying information with any third parties, except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes. SEO Group complies with the Federal Can-Spam Act (15 U.S.C. 7701 et seq.). SEO Group collects the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose. 

##  Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.

##  Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather personal information about visitors or users who are under the age of 13. Primary personal data/Business information Data in which we collect that are voluntarily submitted by each visitor upon creating an account are:

  * Name
  * Profile picture
  * E-mail address
  * Company name
  * Your website address
  * Phone

##  Use of Private Information

We use the personal information we collect from you for the following purposes:

  * To help us learn more about our site visitors and customers and to improve their overall experience and our business
  * To address problems with the Website, our business or our products and services and to protect the security of the Website and our business
  * To contact you occasionally about upcoming promotions and or news about SEO Group

##  Privacy Support

If you have an enquiry or concerns about our privacy policy, please go to the Contact Page.

##  Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of seogroup.com following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

##  Outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover information and data while visiting our website for residents of the United States. Visitors from outside the United States please understand that your information may be processed, stored, or transferred in the United States where our servers are located and where our database is operated. Please be confident that we take reasonable steps to make sure your privacy is protected. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to the facilities we use and those service providers with whom we share it, as stated in our privacy policy. Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Term of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
